小伙伴们  我们要去游轮了
Guys, we're going on a cruise
而且你们和我们同行
and you guys are coming with us.
你们都没得选
None of you have a choice.
游轮  如果我想看
A cruise? If I wanted to watch
一位穿着凉鞋的大块头用手吃东西
a heavy-set guy in sandals eating with his hands,
我只需要待在厨房里
I would've just posted up
看尼克就行了
and watched Nick in the kitchen.
当我俩还在一起时
When we were together,
我们预定了一艘游轮
we booked a cruise.
我们试着把钱要回来
We tried to get our money back,
但那是
but it's...
无法退款的
nonrefundable.
对的
Yeah.
他们的立场很明确
They made that very clear.
当时觉得不会有什么意外的
Seemed like a safe bet at the time.
我们定的游轮不需要退款
I don't want a refund on my cruises
就像我也不会退掉你一样
and I don't want a refund on you.
我们永远不会死的
We're never gonna die!
-对  -你们太恶心了
- Yeah! - Y'all nasty.
好极了
Ah-ha-ha, yeah!
你要去哪
Where you going?
-棒  -你在干嘛
- Yes! - What are you doing now?
原来她要这样
Oh, there she goes...
现在看来  我确实想
Turns out, I do want a refund...
退掉你
on you.
把我的钱还给我
Give me my money back!
不管怎么说  他们同意把我们的情人套间降到
Anyway, they let us downgrade our "Lovers' suite"
可以另外多容纳四个人的房间
to include four more people.
所以你们要去
And that's you guys.
我对和刚刚分手的两个人
I have some concerns about going on a cruise
一起坐游轮有些担心
with two people that just broke up.
-绝对的  -我也是  -对
- Absolutely. - Me, too. - Yeah,
我和温尼的担心一模一样
I have the exact same concern as Winnie.
我不想去
Like, I don't want to go.
我也很不安
I have strong qualms as well.
他很不安
He got qualms.
安心啦
Put those qualms away.
不会有事的  好吗
Yeah. It's gonna be fine, okay?
完全没事  我们已经翻篇了
Totally. We are killing this breakup, honestly.
但我们是要去一艘
But we're gonna be on a ship
在大洋中无处可逃的游轮上
in the middle of the ocean with no escape.
如果你们大吵起来
What if you guys get in a big fight
我们夹在中间怎么办
and we're stuck out there with you?
就像漂浮着的  让你们吃到饱的监狱
It'll be like a floating, all-you-can-eat prison.
我向你们保证
I promise you
不会有异常的
no weirdness
我觉得这倒是个外出
Guess that's an excuse
买比基尼的好借口
to go out and buy a new bikini.
-也许是好事  -我加入
- Which could be good. - I'm in.
开足马力全速前进  已经有两位加入了
Full steam ahead! We have two on board!
不
Nope!
请不要用航海双关语
Let's not do, uh, nautical puns, please.
如果要用航海双关语的话  我们
If we're gonna do nautical puns, we shouldn't...
我们就不应该去了
we shouldn't go.
很合理  我不会用了
That's fair, and I won't.
我也加入
I'm in, too.
我有个主意  供大家参考
Uh, I have an idea. Just throwing this out there.
如果
What if
我们在陆地上
we do the cruise
坐游轮呢
on the ground?
-在地面上  -太二了
- Like, on land. - That's silly.
什么  你是怕坐船吗
What, are you scared of boats or something?
害怕  我会怕坐船
Afraid... me, afraid of boats?
你害怕坐船  哥们
You're afraid of boats, dude.
-你害怕坐船  -等一下
- Ha! He's scared of boats? - Hold on, hold on.
天哪  你害怕坐船
Oh, my God, you're scared of boats.
哥们  是因为船还是水  你能游泳吗
Dude! Is it the boats or the water? Can you swim?
你现在觉得安全了吗
Yeah. You feel safe now?
我不是  我不需要安全
I'm not... I don't need to be safe, man.
我很勇敢
I'm brave!
我来者不拒
I take dumps standing up!
我是纯爷们
I'm a man!
杰茜驾到
第三季  第二十三集
■
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
施密特  你有钓鱼裤
Schmidt, do you got any fisherman's pants
翻译：麦田守望者 小瑶 沐头
借我穿穿吗
I can borrow...?
那是什么
What's that?
翻译：MythCreator 小明 持久君
这是给希希的结业戒指
It's a class ring for Cece.
她在我的辅导下通过了考试  所以
She got her GED and I've been tutoring her, so...
时间轴：Chance-coco   后期：MythCreator
我做了这个
I had this made.
校对：持久君 麦田守望者  总监:  丢丢曳
怎么了
What?
羞  羞  把脸羞
Shame, shame, I know your name...
请不要唱这个  温斯顿
Please don't "Shame, shame" me, Winston.
你仍然爱她
You're still in love with her.
我不爱她了  好吗
I am not still in love with her, okay?
你独自和希希在船上
You're alone on a boat with Cece,
浪漫游轮
romantic cruise,
你还给她珠宝
and you give her jewelry.
-接着呢  -我告诉她我还爱她
- Then what? - I tell her that I'm still in love with her
想让她回到我身边
and that I want her back, and then
接着我们滚床单直到船沉没
we have sex until the boat sinks.
我就知道
I knew it, I knew it!
一直沉到大洋底部
To the bottom of the ocean.
到大洋底部
砂砾  鲭鱼
Oh, man... The sand and the mackerel
鱼饵还有其它那些大洋深处的东西
and the chum and whatever the hell else is down there.
-还有螃蟹  -没螃蟹
- And crabs. - Not the crabs.
-好吧  -别告诉任何人
- Yeah. - Don't tell anyone.
我是认真的  温斯顿  别告诉任何人
I'm serious, Winston. Do not tell anyone.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
你太古怪了
You are so weird.
你能像正常人一样离开房间吗
Can you ever just leave the room like a normal person?
游轮
Cruise! Cruise! Cruise! Cruise!
皇家海星号
游轮
Cruise! Cruise! Yeah!
有点紧促
A little tight.
反正我们接下来要做很多事
With the amount of stuff we're gonna be doing,
很少会待在房间里的
we're barely gonna be in the room.
游轮  游轮
Cruise! Cruise!
游轮  游轮  游轮
Cruise! Cruise. Cruise...
欢迎登上轻舞浪花号
Welcome aboard the Wave Dancer,
在之后的五天里这儿就是你们的家
your home for the next five days.
我是你们的船长  简·诺缇斯
I am your captain, Jan Nortis,
我诚挚地邀请各位与我一同驰骋在浪花上
and I invite you to dance on the waves with me.
游轮  游轮
Cruise! Cruise!
游轮  游轮  邮...
Cruise! Cruise! Cruise! Cru...
我要一醉方休
I'm gonna get drunk!
-对不起  -有激情  我喜欢你们
- Sorry. - Enthusiasm! I like these people.
坚实的友谊是海上冒险中最重要的部分
Friendship is the most crucial ingredient to any sea adventure.
仅次于浮力
Second only to buoyancy.
因为船必须得浮起来
Because a ship has to float.
好吧
Oh, okay.
我刚刚都想不出你该怎么接下去
I didn't know where you was going with it.
我们爱你  船长
We love you, Captain! Whoo-hoo!
大家好  我叫道格
Everybody, my name is Doug.
-你好  道格  -你好  道格
- Hi, Doug. - Hi, Doug.
你好  道格  我是温斯顿
Hey, Doug. I'm Winston.
有人知道遇到紧急情况该怎么办吗
Does anyone know what to do in case of an emergency?
看来我们都一样啊
It looks like we're all in the same boat.
不好意思  如果我们能好好讲正事
Excuse me. If we could just continue on
不用什么航海的双关语的话会比较好
without any more nautical puns, that'd be great.
这样显得很低级趣味
Feels like that's just the lowest form of humor.
看来我们这儿有个暴脾气啊
Looks like I found a Grumpy Gus!
不好意思  什么
I'm sorry, a what?
各位  如果你们见到暴脾气皱着眉
Folks, if you see Gus frowning around,
给他挠挠痒让他开心起来吧
brighten up his day by giving him a tickle.
-什么  -挠痒
- A what? - Tickle.
-停  够了  -挠痒  挠痒痒
- Quit it! Enough! - Tickle. Tickles...
我不喜欢被人挠痒痒  伙计们
I don't like to be tickled, you guys.
-挠痒  挠痒  -好了  够了
- Tickle, tickle... - All right! Enough!
我们是开心了
We have fun!
但是海洋并不开心
But the ocean does not.
什么
What?
如果你们不想死的话
Listen to what I have to say
听清楚我说的话
if you don't want to die.
别担心  教练
Don't worry, Coach.
在游轮上工作的人都是演员
Everyone who works on a cruise ship is a performer.
-他们不过在表演而已  -那又怎样
- They're just doing a show. - So what?
你告诉我这个干吗
What are you talking to me about it for?
-我又不怕  -我只觉得你该知道这些
- I'm not scared. - I just thought you should know.
-你绝对在害怕  -我才不怕  兄弟
- You're definitely scared. - I'm not scared, dude.
-你们在说什么  -好吧  当然
- What are you talking about? - Yeah, no, of course.
-我不怕  -没事的
- I'm not scared. - It's okay.
好的  现在我需要一名志愿者
Okay, now I need a volunteer
帮助我演练一下应急操作步骤
to help me with some emergency procedures.
我来吧  我不在乎
I'll do it. I don't care.
因为我不怕
'Cause I'm not scared.
我要来倾情志愿一把
I'll volunteer my ass off.
我才不怕你
I ain't afraid of you!
-假设现在是下午三点  -下午三点
- Let's say it's 3:00 A.M. - 3:00 A.M.
-突然安全警报响了  -什么
- There's alarms going off... - What?
冰冷的海水没过了你的脚踝
...freezing seawater up to your ankles.
大人惊叫不断  孩子啼哭不停
Adults are screaming, babies are crying!
快  快  动起来  你在甲板上
Go, go, go, go, go! You're up on deck!
有个意大利人在把链条捆到一起
There's an Italian guy strapping chains together!
-你不知道发生了什么  -我知道
- You don't know what's going on! - I know!
-你该做什么  -不知道  我该做什么
- What do you do? - I don't know! What do I do?
-你该做什么  该做什么  -上船吗
- What do you do? What do you do? - I-I get, I get in the boat?
-你上船去  -我上船去
- You get in the boat! - I get in the boat!
你在上船
You're getting in the boat!
-我在上船  -错误
- I get in the boat! - Wrong!
大错特错  你该做的第一件事
Wrong! No! The first thing you do is
是确保你的救生衣牢牢地穿在身上
you make sure your life preserver is strapped on correctly.
不  管它呢  我已经上船了
No, no, screw that, man! I'm gettin' in the boat!
别挡我的路
Get out of my way!
-我在船上了  -你要去哪  教练
- I'm getting in the boat! - Where you going, Coach?
他在往天堂去呢
He's paddling to Heaven,
-因为他已经死了  -别这么说
- 'cause he's already dead. - Don't say that!
展翅吧  小天使
Spread your wings, little angel.
-道格拉斯  过头了  -划桨  划桨
- Douglas... that's a little too much. - Stroke! Stroke!
-这东西有两个  -好的  好吧
- Ah, there's two of these! - Okay... All righty.
-这两个该怎么用啊  -好了
- How do you do two of these? - Okay...
-你很安全  你没事的  -划桨  划桨
- You're safe. You're okay. - Stroke! Stroke!
你很安全
You're okay!
你很安全  很安全
You're okay, you're okay, you're okay.
*Amazing grace*
我不怕船
I'm not afraid of boats.
*How sweet*
没人害怕的
No one's afraid.
*The sound*
-好了  我很好  很好  -好了吗
- Okay, I'm good. I'm good, I'm good. - You okay?
谢谢你
Thank you.
谢谢大家来参加
Thank you all for coming to the...
这个小研讨会
to the seminar.
记得报名参加排球赛
Remember to sign up for the volleyball tournament.
教练
Hey, Coach?
-还好吗  兄弟  -还好吗  朋友
- You okay, buddy? - You okay, pal?
伙计们  我还好  我只是
Nah, you guys, I'm fine. I'm just gonna...
我要在这里玩一会儿  好吗
I'm gonna hang out in the room for a little bit, okay?
-待会儿见  -待会见
- See you later. - Later.
游轮  游轮  游轮
Cruise! Cruise. Cruise...
我们先干点什么
What should we do first?
-开心点  暴脾气  -行了
- Cheer up, Grumpy Gus! - All right!
剪剪你的指甲  兄弟
Cut your fingernails, man! Ha ha!
很棒  这么挠痒不错
Nice! With this tickling.
伙计们  船长来了
Hey, hey, hey, guys. The captain's coming.
船长来了
It's the captain.
有什么事吗  船长
What's up, Captain?
大家好
Hello, again.
我是简·诺缇斯船长
I'm Captain Jan Nortis,
之前已经介绍过了
as I previously stated.
我只是过来说一声
I would just like to say that
我很喜欢你们的激情
I am a fan of your enthusiasm.
别  别  别
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
别这样
Please don't do that.
抱歉
Sorry.
我是船长
I may be a captain,
但是首先
but first and foremost,
我是个女人
I am a woman.
当然
Absolutely.
天哪
Come on!
你们都看到了吗
Did anyone just see
她使劲挑逗尼克
that she was flirting like crazy with Nick?
刚刚那是我见过
That was, like, the most shameless
最不要脸的挑逗了
flirting I've ever seen.
"别掏出那活儿"
"Keep it in your pants"
就是我要跟简·诺缇斯船长说的
is all I have to say to Captain Jan Nortis.
-你不对劲了  -你是不对劲了
- You're being really weird. - You're being weird.
-超级诡异的  -就是这样
- Super weird right now. - Here we go.
已经感觉很微妙了
This is starting now already.
我才没有不对劲
I am not being weird.
你无缘无故就
You're creating an awkward
把氛围弄得这么诡异
situation for no reason.
杰茜  别这样
Don't do this, Jess.
如果这艘船跟那船长一样快
If this ship moves as fast as that captain,
六点就能到恩塞纳达港了[墨西哥港口名]
we'll be in Ensenada by 6:00.
她是在挑逗你
Well, she was flirting with you.
当然我一点都不介意
Which I'm okay with,
因为她长得很漂亮
because she is a handsome woman.
杰茜  够啦  你又开始了
Jess, stop. You're being weird.
不  我一点都不奇怪
No, I'm not being weird.
我真的没有怪怪的
I'm not being weird!
好吧  我是有点奇怪
I am, I am being weird.
好吧  重点在于
Okay, focus up for a second.
这艘船是包含一切服务的
Okay, they say this is an all-inclusive trip,
但是你我都懂这是什么意思
but you know what that means.
但是对他们来说  我们就喝了两杯酒
But from their eyes, you have a couple of drinks,
然后就没了  那我们都付了什么钱啊
and then you're done. And then what have you paid for?
我们可没那么蠢  好吗
We're smarter than that, okay?
-是的  -我们要参加所有的课程
- We are. - We're gonna take every class,
我们要参与所有的项目
we're gonna do every activity.
我们要花得物有所值
We're gonna get our money's worth.
-好的  -懂了吗
- Okay. - Got it?
杰茜卡·戴和尼克·米勒
Uh, Jessica Day and Nick Miller.
好的  戴与米勒的套餐
All right, Day-Miller party.
这是你们豪华浪漫套餐的日程表
Here is your itinerary for the Grand Romance package.
不  不
No! No!
我们想要得是更保守一点
Yeah, we're looking for something more like PG-13.
你们都有什么套餐
What do you have?
你们有基友套餐  或者是...
Do you have, like, a friendship package or...?
你们有什么套餐
What package would you recommend
是给自找麻烦的两兄弟吗
for two brothers looking for trouble?
豪华浪漫套餐是没法退的
The Grand Romance package is nonrefundable.
我们不参加  所以没事
Well, we're not doing that, so we're good.
你确定吗  这有超过六百块的活动...
Are you sure? This includes over $600 of activities and...
-我们要参加  -我们不能参加
- We're gonna do it. - We're not doing it.
六百块
$600?
那是六百张一块钱呢
That is 600 one-dollar bills.
我只能说这么多了
That's the only way I can imagine it.
-我们可以做到的  -好吧
- We can do this. - Okay. Yeah.
我们肯定物有所值
We're gonna get our money's worth.
我们是世上最佳前任
We are the best ex-couple in the whole world.
-是的  -是的
- Yeah, we are. - Yes.
是吧  来吧
Yes. Okay?
你们是前任啊
You guys are exes?
你们肯定不会想参加
Yeah, you're not gonna want to do this.
-我们就是要参加  -日程表拿来
- We're doing it. - Give us the folder.
-我想说...  -暴脾气
- I just wanted to say... - Grumpy Gus!
不不不
No! No! No!
-暴脾气  - 妈呀海怪
- Grumpy Gus. - Sweet mother of sea dragon!
什么  怎么了
What? What happened?
我刚刚看到一只海豚
I just witnessed a dolphin
被我们船底割成了两半
being cut straight in half by our keel.
恐怖的景象
It's a ghastly sight.
什么
What?
太恐怖了
That's horrible!
太可怕了
Terrible.
可怜的海豚啊
It's a shame about the dolphin, man.
真的好可怜
Really is.
怎么了
What?!
当你们的身体结为一体
As your bodies become one,
跟随着流淌而过的气息
follow your breath
从你的脊椎到你的脚底
through your spine to the soles of your feet
最后进入你的生殖器
and into your genitals.
什么
What?
进入我的生殖器
Into my genitals?
对啊
Yeah.
进到你的生殖器
Into your genitals...
我才不要让气息进到我的生殖器呢  女士
I'm not breathing into my genitals, lady.
来吧  小情侣  性感点
All right, lovers, let's get sexy.
给我一个最性感的姿势
Give me your sexiest pose right here.
-就是这样  就是了  -最性感的
- This is it. This is it. - Sexiest pose.
一点都不...  毫无浪漫可言
That's not... it's not romantic in any way.
想想你们的初吻  什么感觉
Think about the first time you kissed. How was it?
靠近一点
If you can move in.
靠过来
Come back in.
回来
我从来没做过前任的情侣按摩
Wow, I've never done a couples massage on exes before.
如果你想问的话  他背上的疤
In case you're wondering what that scar on his back is,
是他六岁时从围墙上摔下来弄的
it's from falling on a fence when he was six.
我当时死了有十分钟
I was legally dead for ten minutes.
要把毛巾摆成
We're going to make all the towel animals
你们夜夜看到的动物
you guys find in your rooms every single night!
-我们摆成了衣服  -漂亮
- We made laundry. - Nice.
*We're always happy*
*Life's for living, yeah, that's our philosophy*
我们就是完全不同的人
We're just totally different people.
我们就不应该在一起
Yeah, we just don't belong together.
你们真的让我很无语
You're really bumming me out.
杰茜  你是不是眼里也进沙子了
Hey, Jess, is this doing weird stuff to your eyes?
是啊
Definitely.
来击个掌  别理我
Give me five, man! Leaving me hanging!
你猜怎么着  你是对的
You know what? You were right.
一点都不奇怪
This isn't weird at all.
一点都不
No, it isn't.
他们没有玫瑰葡萄酒了吗
Are they out of rosé?
知道吗
You know what?
这是个古老的调酒技巧  杰茜
This is an old bartending trick, Jess.
拿稳你的杯子  像这样
Put your glass out. You go like this...
这不可能
No way.
你看  又有玫瑰葡萄酒了
Look at that. You got some rosé.
你是天才
You're a genius.
我认为我在海上会更聪明
I think I'm smarter at sea.
你看起来
You look,
你看起来就属于这里
you look like you belong here.
什么意思  属于船吗
What's that, on a ship?
你也是
Yeah, you, too.
那是个错误决定
Well, that was a mistake.
可不是吗
Yes, it was!
不是故意的
That was not on purpose.
-也有我的错  -对  是的  那是
- My fault, too. - Yep. Yeah, it was...
我们不能再享受这个豪华浪漫套餐了
We can't do the Grand Romance package anymore.
同意  我们应该
I agree. We should...
太多了  太激烈了
No. It's too much. It's too intense.
它们会让你产生狂热的性需求  我知道
They whip you into this sexual frenzy. I know.
好奇怪  我只是觉得
It's weird. I just feel like...
因为所有的事都挺好
Yeah, 'cause everything's fine.
我今晚感觉自己就像艘游艇
You know, I feel like a cruise tonight.
那不麻烦  我感觉像
It's not, like, a really big deal. I feel like...
我们很好  一切都很好
We're good. Everything's good.
是的  没问题  没问题
Yeah, no problem, no problem.
-好了  再见-  -再见
- All right, bye, dude. - Bye.
杰茜  我到处找你
Jess, I've been looking all over for you.
我希望作为一个团队  可以玩玩夜钓
I was hoping that as a group, we could do a little night fishing...
我都已经付了定金了
that I already put a deposit down on,
所以我们得去
so we're going.
如果我们什么都没钓到
And if we don't catch anything,
他们会让我们直接用机枪向水里面扫射
they'll let us shoot a machine gun directly into the water.
那就是国际海域的意义所在
That is international waters for you, baby.
我除了和你一去出去然后在你面前
I would really love nothing more than to go out there
射上一堆鱼外没有更喜欢做的事了
and shoot a bunch of fish in the face with you,
但我觉得那更像是尼克会做的
but I think that's more of a Nick thing.
就在昨天  我们决定分开活动
And yesterday, we decided it would be better for everyone
那样对所有人都好
if we just spent the rest of the time apart.
什么
What?
我真的很抱歉  我希望这次旅行
I'm really sorry. I wanted this
能让你们感觉超棒
to be a great vacation for you guys.
但是  我们划分了一下船的区域
But look, we split up the ship:
我占了右舷  他占另一边
I took starboard, he took the other one.
我挑了右舷  她得到了另一边
I got the starboard and she got the other side.
你在做什么呢
What are you doing, man?
在排气孔边上待着
You're hanging out by an exhaust vent.
能让我的左脸保持温暖
It keeps the left side of my face warm
而且声音听起来很像大海
and it sounds like the ocean.
比大海本身还像吗
More than the ocean sounds like the ocean?
尼克  你们可不能整个旅程都单独活动
Come on, Nick. You guys can't be separate the whole trip.
分手太难  这趟旅行让这点更明显
The trip just made it clear. The breakup's too hard.
我觉得我们一时半会儿是当不了朋友的
I don't think we can be friends for a while.
什么  你不和杰茜当普通朋友吗
What? You're not gonna be friends with Jess?
你们都那么说了  就是感觉很奇怪
And even you guys said it. It's just too weird.
尼克  那听起来就像总统和副总统
Nick, man, that's like the president and the vice president
不是好朋友
not being best friends.
他们当然不是好朋友
They're not best friends.
谁说的  所有人都知道他们是好朋友
Come on. Everybody knows they're best friends.
他们在一起工作  但不是好朋友
They work together, but they're not best friends.
伙计  那是总统
Dude, they're the president
- 和副总统啊  -好吧
- and the vice president. - Okay.
这样你能接受吗
I mean, is this something you're okay with?
不能  我不能接受  但我还能怎样呢
No, I'm not okay, but what am I gonna do?
我想说
Well... I mean, look, man,
这次旅行我们都要在一起
we all have to be together on this trip.
那是我们出来玩的目的
That's why we came here.
尼克
Nick,
肯定有我能做的
there's gotta be something I can do.
没错  你知道你能做什么吗
Yeah, you know what you can do?
什么都行  说吧
Yeah, anything, come on.
你可以在船的另一头兑现
You can cash in my skee ball tickets
我的滑雪球球票
on the other side of the boat.
给我拿一个之前
Get me one of those toy spiders
和你说过的蜘蛛玩具
that I was talking to you about before.
-如果没了  -行了行了
- And if they're out... - All right, man, all right.
你能给我带一些橡皮吗
...can you grab me a bunch of erasers?
机会没有如我所愿的出现
The opportunity has not presented itself
所以我要创造机会
as I'd hoped it would, so I'm creating it now.
我会说  愿我们的后代沐浴在
When I say, "May our progeny bathe
永恒之光中  那是给你的暗示
in the infinite glow," that's your cue.
我  我刚才说了什么
Now, what... what did I just say?
你重复一遍让我确定你懂了
You repeat it so I know that you know the cue.
愿我们的  什么东西来着
May our pro... What?
你用脚趾头记事吗  真受不了
What's wrong with you? Unbelievable.
我不知道你说的是什么东西
I don't know what you're saying.
我就说走你  可以了吧
I'll just say, "Go," Okay?
我说走你的时候  你就开始演奏
When I say, "Go," You start to play.
在她看见之前  躲到排气孔后面
And before she sees, just get behind... get behind the vent.
排气孔后面
Get behind the vent.
希希
Cece...
月光掩映下的你的秀发
Um, your hair in the moonlight...
好闪亮
it looks so shiny.
我想找个信号好的地方和伯斯特聊天
You know, I'm trying to get a signal so I can talk to Buster,
但在这里完全没希望
but it's just impossible out here.
月光下  你的双眼
In the moonlight, your eyes,
就像  就像鱼眼一样炯炯有神
they sparkle like, like fish eyes.
有了  怎么  我得一直
I got one. Now, like, what, do I have to hold it
保持这个角度吗
at this angle the whole time?
为什么和伯斯特聊天这么重要
Why is it so important for you to get in touch with Buster?
你比任何人都明白
Look, you know better than anyone
我和人谈恋爱总是没有好运气
that I don't have the best of luck with relationships.
我也知道你认为他对我而言太年轻
And I know you think he's young for me.
我没这么想
I don't.
我只希望你开心
I just want you to be happy.
谢谢
Thank you.
伙计们  伙计们
Guys, guys!
你们得跟我来  现在
You got to come with me right now.
警告一声
Be warned, though,
有个拿着小提琴的怪人
there is a weird guy with a violin
-藏在这通风口后面  -有个什么人
- hiding behind this vent. - A what?
伙计
Dude!
-怎么回事  -来吧  好了
- What's going on? - Come on... right.
我  我要原地打晕你  先生
I will... I will knock you out where you stand, sir.
站回去
Get back there.
他们暂时不想当朋友了
They're gonna take a break from being friends for a while?
-什么意思  -伙计们  这是我们的责任
- What does that even mean? - Guys, this is on us.
是我们施加的压力
We're the ones who put the pressure
让他们不要表现得奇怪
on them to not be weird.
我知道  我们想啥呢
I know. What were we thinking?
他们怎么可能不表现得奇怪  他们才刚刚分手
Of course they're gonna be weird. They just broke up.
全是你们的责任  我可什么都没做
Hey, that's on y'all. I-I have nothing to do with that.
我一直在屋里待着消遣
I've just been chilling in the room.
随便转转  唱几首歌
Hanging out, singing songs.
*你在房间里很安全*
*You are safe in the room*
*你很安全  你能活下去*
*You are safe, you will live...*
我整个早晨都在尝试
I've been trying to get them to talk
让他们谈谈  知道吗
to each other all morning, okay?
我还舍弃了早餐披萨
I passed up on breakfast pizza
和单身派对
and singles bingo.
那些单身的小妞
And those bingo chicks?
她们都饥不可耐了  好极了
Oh, they put out. Bingo!
他们不会听劝的
They're not gonna listen to us.
别再那样做了
Don't-don't ever do that again.
我刚说的那个吗  她们就是
The bingo thing? That's what they...
很好玩的  他们是这么说的
It's funny, that's what they say.
你知道他们会听谁的吗
You know who they will listen to, though?
-医生  总统  -船...
- A doctor. The president! - The ca...
你想说谁
What were you...
-你想说谁  -船长
- What were you gonna say? - The captain.
船长
The captain.
请注意  我是船长
Attention, this is your captain.
能否请尼克·米勒和杰茜卡·戴
Would Nick Miller and Jessica Day
回到他们的包房
please return to their stateroom
这是基于一个没有生命威胁  却十分必要的
for a non-life-threatening but necessary
官方的海事原因
official maritime reason.
这不是紧急事件
This is not an emergency.
绝对不是
It is definitely not.
-你听到船长广播了吗  -听到了
- Did you hear the captain? - Yes!
快  快  快
Go, go, go!
大家快进来  这不是演习
Everybody inside! This is not a drill!
好了
Okay!
好  门锁好了
Okay, the door is locked.
"请勿打扰"的牌子也已经挂好了
The "Do not disturb" sign has been employed.
除非你们重新建立友谊
We are not leaving here
否则我们就不离开
until you guys are friends again.
我们只是想单独度过假期
We just wanted to spend our vacation alone.
-没错  -待在船的不同位置
- Yes. - On separate strange parts of this ship.
-就是  -我很想看船是怎么运转的
- Yeah, it's... - I really wanted to see how the ship worked.
-我觉得很有意思  -而我很想看
- I think it's interesting. - And I really wanted to see
船的另一边是怎么运转的
how the other side of the ship worked.
-对  -很有意思
- Yeah. - It's interesting.
我们不该要求你们
We should've never asked you guys
不要表现得很奇怪
not to be weird around us.
我们  我们希望你们在我们周围奇怪点
We-we want you to be weird around us.
-没错  -让我们帮你们吧
- Yeah. - Just let us in.
敞开心扉
Open your cellar doors,
让我们也体验一下你们的感受
and let us taste your jams.
-你想"体会我们的感受"  -重复一遍  我没明白你的意思
- You want to "Taste our jams"? - Again, you have lost me.
听听你自己在说些什么  一次也好
Listen to yourself for once in your life.
那是属于我的感受  你体会不来
It's my jam and you can't have it.
首先  那是我的
First of all, that's my
-我前女友的感受  伙计们  -我给它封上封条
- ex-girlfriend's jam, dude. - I put a ban on jam.
好吧  知道吗  我们所有人都很奇怪
Okay, you know what? All of us are weird.
但我们还是朋友
But we're all still friends.
所以  来好好谈谈
So, let's talk about it.
我先说
I'll go first.
我跟
I've made out
这个房间里半数的人都有过一段
with half of the guys in this room.
好吧
Okay.
这是个开始  -好的
- That's a start. - All right.
这是个开始
That's a start.
而我  有过一些和
And I have had nightmares
这房间里的两位男士亲热的噩梦
about making out with the other two guys in this room.
-其中一个人是你自己  -还有我
- So, yourself? - And me.
-尼克和温斯顿  -好吧  好吧
- Nick and Winston. - Okay. Okay.
你终于承认了  太好了
It's good for you to finally admit that.
我很佩服你
I respect that.
没错  感谢分享
Yeah, thanks for sharing.
我被吓坏了
Um, it really bums me out
因为我从没想过  自己会如此享受
that I'll never know the infinite joy
那种好像有个孩子怀在肚子里的感觉
of what it feels like to carry a child inside of me.
好的  教练
Okay, Coach!
非常诚实
That's honest.
非常诚实  就这样
That's real honest. That's how it's done.
好了
Okay, um...
好的  关键的来了
Here we go, up we go.
我觉得非常奇怪  因为
I feel like it is really weird that...
我还跟前男友住在同一个屋檐下
I live with my ex-boyfriend.
-看  说出来了  -不错
- See? There you go! - Nice!
-就这样敞开心扉  说出来  -非常好
- Just turn on the tap. You know, let it out. - Really nice.
你能说出来真是太好了
That was cool that you admitted that.
还跟前女友住在一起我也觉得很奇怪
I feel weird about living with my ex-girlfriend.
你知道  这是潜在的麻烦
Yeah. You know, I think it's a landmine for trouble.
家里要是来了帅哥该怎么办
What's gonna happen when other hunks come around?
你要是带回来小贱货该怎么办
What's gonna happen when you bring some ho-bag in the house?
没错  那很吓人  而且我觉得
Exactly! Like, that... it's scary stuff, and I feel like
人们分手之后  一般都会保持距离
when a breakup happens, you mostly get away.
因为我会揍她的
'Cause I'm gonna beat her ass.
她要是比你壮怎么办
What if she's bigger than you?
很有可能
She probably will be.
少来了  这个笑话好
Oh, snap! That was good.
很好
Good for you!
没错  我就知道  伙计
Yeah! I saw that, man.
就是这样  都是这样开始的
That's how it all starts. This is how it starts.
-很好  -很好伙计  非常好
- Good. - That's good, man, that's really good.
对
Yeah.
很高兴能跟你说这个
Well, it's nice to talk to you about this.
昨晚你想要亲我
Yeah, it was really weird when you...
还有舔我耳朵的时候
tried to kiss me last night,
真的很诡异
and you licked my ear.
-什么  什么 -你们昨晚接吻了
- What?! What?! - You guys kissed last night?
-这也太乱了  -什么
- This is so confusing! - What?!
那只是一时错乱  我们喝醉了
It was just a lapse. We were drunk.
你们复合了吗
You guys are getting back together?
我们没有复合
We're not getting back together.
你们弄得大家都迷茫了
You're confusing everybody!
不  都是因为奢华浪漫套餐
No, it was the Grand Romance package.
天哪
My God!
里面那些  像叠那些毛巾
They were, like, folding these towels.
太情色了  你试试那样叠毛巾
It was so sexy. You try folding towels
看你会不会有反应
like that and see if you don't get turned on.
没错  因为他们把毛巾叠得跟阴道似得
Yeah, because they fold the towels like vaginas.
那是天鹅  伙计
They're swans, dude.
还有瑜伽教练说什么
And the yoga instructor was, like, breathing
用生殖器深呼吸
into our genitals, and, like...
大家都发春了
It opened everyone up.
是啊
Yeah.
明显得很
In a real true way.
没错
Absolutely.
小鸡鸡已经准备
This thing was ready to talk
再跟它的另一半谈谈了
to that thing again.
-情感上加肉体上的  -没错
- Emotionally and sexually. - Yeah.
-什么  -你们这是有什么毛病  伙计
- What?! What?! - What's wrong with you, man?
-你们疯了吗  -选一个吧
- Are you crazy? - Just pick one-- either
你们是在一起还是没有
you're together or you're not!
我要打你个脸上开花  兄弟
Gonna punch you in the face, bro!
实在是诡异
Things are really weird.
我赞同
Agreed.
但我还能接受
But I'm okay with it.
-我也是  -嘿
- Me, too. - Hey, there.
什么  好吧
What? All right, okay.
-挺好的  好的开始  -棒极了
- Good enough, good start. - Wonderful.
谢谢你们的调解
Thank you for doing this weird intervention thing.
-挺好的  -是啊  卓有成效
- This was pretty great. - Yeah, it worked out.
我觉得大家都没事了
I think everybody's good now.
我们去吃假蟹肉长肉肉吧
Let's go eat our weight in fake crab.
-走你  -那必须的  走着
- There you go. - Absolutely. There we go.
好主意  一醉方休
Great idea. I'm gonna get drunk.
我要嗨起来
I gotta get psyched up.
要嗨起来
Gotta get psyched up.
门卡住了  是你们策划的吗
The door's stuck. Is that part of your thing?
-不是  -快叫保安
- No. - Well, call security.
我把房间电话给切了
I got rid of the room phone.
我以为这会
I-I thought it was gonna be
比这激烈得多的  对不起
more intense than this, I-I'm sorry!
你谋杀了我们
You murdered us!
-开门  开门  -什么  不
- Open up! Open up! - What? No.
-小心  -知道吗
- Watch out. - You know what?
一般  一般都是把手的问题
It's just, it's usually the handle.
-弄下把手  -我来  我来
- Just, like, get the handle... - I'll do it, I'll do it!
-交给我吧  -好吧  让开  交给我
- I got it. - All right, move. I got it.
-伙计们  伙计们  -开始吧
- Guys, guys, guys! - Okay, here we go.
冷静
Calm down.
要多久才会有人听见我们求救
How long could it take for someone to hear us?
我们在浴缸里做了不好的事
We did bad things to the tub.
我的神啊
我找到糖了
I got the sugars.
我是小糖人
I'm the sugar man.
闭嘴  说话皂在我手上
Silence! I have the talking soap!
我是周三女王
I'm the queen of Wednesday!
有张全家福真好
It's so nice to have a family portrait.
我们应该少洗点澡
We should shower less.
我觉得我们看起来棒极了
I think we look really great.
把这框起来太好了
I'm really glad we framed this.
多么光荣的一刻
I mean, what a proud moment.
上报还挺酷的
It is cool being in the paper, though.
那个胆小的我在船上死去了
Part of me died on that boat.
我再也不会那样了
Oh. I will never be the same again.
好吧  伙计  去歇会儿
All right, man. Take a nap.
睡一觉就忘了  伙计
Sleep it off, man.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
希希是在凝望施密特吗
Is Cece checking out Schmidt?
什么
What?!
让我看看
Let me see that.
你在说什么呢  温斯顿
What are you talking about, Winston?
羞羞
Shame, shame,
把脸羞
I know your name.
你不知道我的名字  温斯顿
You do not know my name, Winston.
希希曾有男友叫贝蒂
Cece got a boyfriend who used to be Betty!
你最好快点跑  贱人
Yeah, you better run, bitch.
我的胡子
My mustache!
我一直在想
You know, I've been thinking a lot
-你们的睡觉协议  -诡异
- about your sleeping arrangements and... - Weird.
我或许有个主意
I might have an idea on how to make things
能让事情不那么诡异
a little bit less weird.
真的吗  是什么
Really? What is it?
三个字
Two words.
-上下铺  -不
- Bunk beds. - No.
不  我才不要在房里放张上下铺  施密特
No, I'm not putting bunk beds in my room, Schmidt.
不放你房间  放我房间
Not in your room. In my room.
就跟大学时一样  伙计
It'll be just like college, my man.
只是多了很多爱爱罢了
Only with way more sex.
-什么  -我说错了
- What? - That came out wrong.
我才不要跟你睡上下铺  施密特
I'm not bunking with you, Schmidt.
不  他跟你睡
Yeah, he is.
是啊  他跟我睡
好吧  我跟你睡
Yeah, he is.
那一定要有很多规矩
There's gonna be a lot of rules,
而且大部分要我来定
and I'm gonna make most of them.
全都给你定  伙计
You can make them all, man!
除了我定的之外
Except for the ones that I make!
先来后到嘛
First one in gets dibs!
新闻
发现野生游客